<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sentiment on Text Machine Lab</title>
    <link>/lab2/tags/sentiment/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sentiment on Text Machine Lab</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    
	<atom:link href="/lab2/tags/sentiment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>RuSentiment: An Enriched Sentiment Analysis Dataset for Social Media in Russian</title>
      <link>/lab2/projects/rusentiment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/lab2/projects/rusentiment/</guid>
      <description>We present RuSentiment, a new dataset for sentiment analysis of social media posts in Russian. RuSentiment is currently the largest in its class for Russian, with 30,521 posts annotated with Fleiss&amp;rsquo; kappa of 0.58 (3 annotations per post). To diversify the dataset, 6,749 posts were pre-selected with an active learning-style strategy. We report baseline classification results, and we also release the best-performing embeddings trained on 3.2B tokens of Russian VKontakte posts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TwitterHawk - a Twitter Sentiment Analysis System</title>
      <link>/lab2/projects/twitterhawk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/lab2/projects/twitterhawk/</guid>
      <description>TwitterHawk is an open-source natural language processing system for Twitter sentiment analysis. This system was developed for the SemEval-2015 Task 10: Sentiment Analysis in Twitter. The system placed 1st in topic-based sentiment classification (Subtask C), and ranked 6th out of 40 in identifying the sentiment of sarcastic tweets (for Subtask B). The system also placed 5th/11 for Subtask A (sentiment of a tweet&#39;s sub-phrase), 10th/40 for Subtask B (sentiment of a full tweet), and 3rd/6 for Subtask D (summarization of Subtask C).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>