<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Peoples on Text Machine Lab</title>
    <link>/lab2/people/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Peoples on Text Machine Lab</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    
	<atom:link href="/lab2/people/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/lab2/people/daviddonahue/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/lab2/people/daviddonahue/</guid>
      <description>Hi! I am an undergraduate Electrical Engineering/Computer Science double major at Text Machine Lab, University of Massachusetts Lowell. My current work focuses on using Generative Adversarial Network (GAN) models to plan and generate natural language. As a side project I have been creating models for dialogue generation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/lab2/people/gregsmelkov/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/lab2/people/gregsmelkov/</guid>
      <description>Hi, I&#39;m a sophomore studying Computer Science at UMass Lowell. I am currently interning at the Text Machine Laboratory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/lab2/people/mattdowney/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/lab2/people/mattdowney/</guid>
      <description>Greetings! this is the webpage of Matthew Downey. Currently I am a Mechanical Engineering student persuing minor in Computer Science, going into my sophmore year at Umass Lowell. Interning in the text Machine Lab, I assist the researchers with their projects. Along with this, I study ML and its use in NLP.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/lab2/people/patrickkyoyetera/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/lab2/people/patrickkyoyetera/</guid>
      <description>Hello! I graduated from the University of Massachusetts Lowell with a Bachelor of Science in Computer Science with a focus on Data Science&amp;hellip;. &amp;laquo;&amp;raquo; lol</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/lab2/people/victoriakhaychuk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/lab2/people/victoriakhaychuk/</guid>
      <description>Hi! I am an intern at Text Machine Lab, University of Massachusetts Lowell. I am studying to become a data scientist. Beyond taking programming and statistics courses, my goal is to learn machine learning with Python.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BS, now at MIT EECS</title>
      <link>/lab2/people/williamboag/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/lab2/people/williamboag/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BS, now at MITRE Corporation</title>
      <link>/lab2/people/kevinwacome/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/lab2/people/kevinwacome/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PhD student</title>
      <link>/lab2/people/olgakovaleva/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/lab2/people/olgakovaleva/</guid>
      <description>Hi! I am a PhD student at Text Machine Lab, University of Massachusetts Lowell. My background is in Applied Mathematics and I currently focus on representation learning problems in ML. My work also includes building NLP models for question answering and analyzing electronic health records.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PhD student</title>
      <link>/lab2/people/saurabhkulshreshtha/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/lab2/people/saurabhkulshreshtha/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PhD student</title>
      <link>/lab2/people/vladlialin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/lab2/people/vladlialin/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PhD, now at IBM Watson</title>
      <link>/lab2/people/yen-fuluo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/lab2/people/yen-fuluo/</guid>
      <description>My expertise includes Natural Language Processing, Machine Learning, and Data Visualization. My thesis: &amp;ldquo;Mining the Clinical Narrative: Mortality Prediction and Concept Normalization&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PhD, now at Microsoft</title>
      <link>/lab2/people/alexeyromanov/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/lab2/people/alexeyromanov/</guid>
      <description>I am currently a fourth year Ph.D. student at UMass Lowell in the Text-Machine Lab working with Anna Rumshisky. My research interests at this moment are particularly focused on applying Deep Learning methods in Natural Language Processing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PhD, now at Microsoft Research</title>
      <link>/lab2/people/peterpotash/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/lab2/people/peterpotash/</guid>
      <description>I received a Masters in Mathematics and a PhD in Computer Science. My dissertation focused on deep learning strategies for argument mining. I currently work at MSR Maluuba.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PhD, now at Nuance</title>
      <link>/lab2/people/yuanliangmeng/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/lab2/people/yuanliangmeng/</guid>
      <description>I am interested in many aspects of natural language processing, deep learning and AI. Currently I work on temporal relation information extraction and coreference resolution. I studied engineering in the past, and was a software engineer before joining the lab. Besides NLP, I also had some experience in speech sysnthesis and computer vision.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PI</title>
      <link>/lab2/people/annarumshisky/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/lab2/people/annarumshisky/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Postdoc</title>
      <link>/lab2/people/annarogers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/lab2/people/annarogers/</guid>
      <description>I am a post-doctoral associate at the Computer Science Department, University of Massachusetts (Lowell). I hold a Ph.D. degree from the Department of Language and Information Sciences at the University of Tokyo (Japan). My research spans the intersection of linguistics, natural language processing, and machine learning.
This page lists my work with Text Machine lab, which I joined in 2017. See my full research profile here.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>